<?xml version="1.0"?>
<scenes>
  <scene id="1" bgImage="testi1">
    <options>
      <option id="3">
        Throw a flower pot at the ghost
      </option>
      <option id="3">
        Express your disgust at the floating ectoplasm
      </option>
      <option id="3">
        Bow your head and greet the man with your most corteous gestures
      </option>
    </options>
    <desc>
      <![CDATA[
        You see a sturdy green door in front of you, it's paint peeling off and revealing a brown oak surface. Above the door a plaque reads: ”Archive room”. A large round handle and an iron lock are embedded into the strong door.

        You take the key in your hand and place it into the lock. It requires some force to get through the rust and dust. A loud creak echoes in the hallway and behind the door. The lock moans and grinds and finally rewards you with a satisfying click. You push the grand door open and cover your mouth from all the dust puffing around. After coughing a few times you raise your eyes to the archive room and see right in front of you a ghostly apparition of a high class man. The man appears as a white and partly transparent ghost. He even waves his hands around a bit and lets out a meager ”OoooOooOOOoooOooOOooo...” You are not impressed.
        
        Behind the ghost you see rows of archive cabinets, one of them no doubt holding within the details that you seek.
      ]]>
    </desc>
  </scene>
  <scene id="2" bgImage="testi2">
    <options>
      <option id="3">
        ”Hey, no need to alarm yourself. I mean, do I look like a person to worry about?”
      </option>
      <option id="1">
        ”Step out of my way or I'll do terrible things!” shake fist in air
      </option>
      <option id="3">
        ”Whoa, please don't hurt me, I am just a lost patient!”
      </option>
    </options>
    <desc>
      <![CDATA[
        You find a door with a plaque next to it saying: ”Guard's room.” You open the door and step in to find the key. A gruesome scene opens before you: a stone altar with a mutilated sheep body on it lies in the middle of the room. With your step you hear a crunch and notice the floor of the room is filled with pieces of broken flower pots. A small window on the side wall lets in some moonlight.

        On the altar edge sits a silver cup. Upon closer inspection you see it is filled with blood. As per the instructions of the crazy man, you dip your hand into the warm blood and feel the bottom of the cup until a small object finds it's way into your hand. You raise your hand from the blood and shake your hand wildly to rid yourself of the goo. Between your fingers is now a small key.

        Startled by a grunt you turn around to see a person in guard uniform wielding a butcher's knife and in the other hand hanging a sheep head by its' ear. You ready your words and prepare to talk your way through this.
      ]]>
    </desc>
  </scene>
  <scene id="3" bgImage="testi3">
    <options>
      <option id="2">
        Option1 text 3
      </option>
      <option id="1">
        Option2 text 3
      </option>
      <option id="3">
        Option3 text 3
      </option>
    </options>
    <desc>
      <![CDATA[
      Long
      description text
      3
      ]]>
    </desc>
  </scene>
</scenes>